const questions = {
  1: [
    {
      id: '622a1c347cc59eab6f94f891',
      question: 'With which sport is David Beckham associated?',
      category: 'Sport & Leisure',
      difficulty: 1,
      allAnswers: ['Hockey', 'Tennis', 'Football', 'Surfing'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: '624334dfcfaae40c1296146f',
      question: 'What would you call a baby owl?',
      category: 'Science',
      difficulty: 1,
      allAnswers: ['A Caterpillar', 'An Owlet', 'A Colt', 'A Codling'],
      corrAnsIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: '6256985c9da29df7b05f7282',
      question: 'In the Marvel Cinematic Unvierse, which character is played by Scarlett Johansson?',
      category: 'Film & TV',
      difficulty: 1,
      allAnswers: ['Gamora', 'Valkyrie', 'Black Widow', 'Captain Marvel'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c3e7cc59eab6f952331',
      question: 'By what process is rock worn down by the weather?',
      category: 'Science',
      difficulty: 1,
      allAnswers: ['Sediment', 'Vegetation', 'Erosion', 'Sublimation'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c9b',
      question: "Who was the author of 'A Christmas Carol'?",
      category: 'Arts & Literature',
      difficulty: 1,
      allAnswers: ['Thomas Hardy', 'Jane Austen', 'Charles Dickens', 'Edgar Allen Poe'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
  ],
  2: [
    {
      id: '62602d5f4b176d54800e3c93',
      question: 'Which of these cities is in Denmark?',
      category: 'Geography',
      difficulty: 2,
      allAnswers: ['Copenhagen', 'Athens', 'Munich', 'Milan'],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: '6242cb59d543524f1b19c925',
      question: 'What is the word for a group of lions?',
      category: 'Science',
      difficulty: 2,
      allAnswers: ['A muster', 'A clowder', 'A pride', 'A shrewdness'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c367cc59eab6f9503dd',
      question: 'What Is Worn Around The Neck To Keep Vampires Away?',
      category: 'Society & Culture',
      difficulty: 2,
      allAnswers: ['Chili', 'Garlic', 'Silver', 'A Crucifix'],
      corrAnsIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c377cc59eab6f950577',
      question: 'What is Cosmology the study of?',
      category: 'Science',
      difficulty: 2,
      allAnswers: ['the cosmos or our place in it', 'beetles', 'flags', 'study of the mouth and its diseases'],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: '624c60d150d1a5e051325a75',
      question: 'Where in the world would you most expect to be served a taco?',
      category: 'Food & Drink',
      difficulty: 2,
      allAnswers: ['Mexico', 'Japan', 'Brazil', 'Bhutan'],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
  ],
  3: [
    {
      id: '622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951031',
      question: 'What is the mathematical term used to describe the shape of a cell in a honeycomb? ',
      category: 'Science',
      difficulty: 3,
      allAnswers: ['Hexagon', 'Octagon', 'Dodecahedron', 'Pentagon'],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c357cc59eab6f94fda4',
      question: 'Which Duo Had A Hit With The Song "Islands In The Stream"?',
      category: 'Music',
      difficulty: 3,
      allAnswers: [
        'Kenny Rogers & Dolly Parton',
        'Michael and Janet Jackson',
        'Bob Dylan and Joan Baez',
        'Sonny and Cher',
      ],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c377cc59eab6f950565',
      question: 'What is Dendrochronology the study of?',
      category: 'Science',
      difficulty: 3,
      allAnswers: [
        'the scientific study of muscles',
        'minerals',
        'the age of trees and the records in their rings',
        'venereal diseases',
      ],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: '623389510161109f922aacdf',
      question: 'Which US state capital is known as the mile high city?',
      category: 'Geography',
      difficulty: 3,
      allAnswers: ['Denver ', 'Austin', 'Sacramento', 'Columbus'],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c387cc59eab6f950ba4',
      question: "Which American band released the song 'Boom Boom Pow'?",
      category: 'Music',
      difficulty: 3,
      allAnswers: ['MercyMe', 'Three 6 Mafia', 'Black Eyed Peas', 'The Velvet Underground'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
  ],
  4: [
    {
      id: '622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd09',
      question: "Which philosopher famously said 'The only thing I know is that I know nothing'?",
      category: 'Society & Culture',
      difficulty: 4,
      allAnswers: ['Socrates', 'Bertrand Russell', 'Immanuel Kant', 'Thomas Hobbes'],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c3c7cc59eab6f95197a',
      question: 'What happened on the 21st July 1969?',
      category: 'History',
      difficulty: 4,
      allAnswers: [
        'First Manned moon landing',
        'The Internet was invented',
        'World War 2 ended',
        'John F Kennedy was assassinated',
      ],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: '625e9ea727d267462ff91758',
      question: 'Which of these colors would you find on the flag of Indonesia?',
      category: 'Geography',
      difficulty: 4,
      allAnswers: ['Red', 'Orange', 'Green', 'Yellow'],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a9c',
      question: "On May 1st 1931 the world's then tallest building was opened in New York City. Which building was it?",
      category: 'History',
      difficulty: 4,
      allAnswers: ['The Chrysler Building', 'The World Trade Center', 'The Empire State Building', 'The CN Tower'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: '625e9dc7796f721e95543f2c',
      question: 'What does the flag of Argentina look like?',
      category: 'Geography',
      difficulty: 4,
      allAnswers: [
        'Three horizontal bands of sky blue, white, and sky blue, with a yellow sun in the center.',
        'Two equal horizontal bands of white and red.',
        'Red with a yellow sun having eight broadening rays extending to the edges.',
        'Red with a white cross that extends to the edges.',
      ],
      corrAnsIndex: 0,
    },
  ],
  5: [
    {
      id: '622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa34',
      question: 'The painting "The Third of May" by ‎Francisco Goya is a part of which art movement?',
      category: 'Arts & Literature',
      difficulty: 5,
      allAnswers: ['Dutch and Flemish Renaissance', 'Romanticism', 'Abstract expressionism', 'Crystal Cubism'],
      corrAnsIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c367cc59eab6f9500b0',
      question: 'In American Football, where is the Orange Bowl?',
      category: 'Sport & Leisure',
      difficulty: 5,
      allAnswers: ['Dallas', 'Miami', 'Atlanta', 'Los Angeles'],
      corrAnsIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c397cc59eab6f950fb2',
      question: 'Who Opened The First Cinema In Paris In 1895?',
      category: 'General Knowledge',
      difficulty: 5,
      allAnswers: ['The Warner Brothers', 'The Cannes Brothers', 'The Lumiere Brothers', 'The Canal Brothers'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa1b',
      question: 'Which artist painted "Three Musicians"',
      category: 'Arts & Literature',
      difficulty: 5,
      allAnswers: ['Henri Matisse', 'Sandro Botticelli', 'Pablo Picasso', 'Georges Seurat'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: '622a1c397cc59eab6f950d4f',
      question: "Which band includes 'Ian Anderson'?",
      category: 'Music',
      difficulty: 5,
      allAnswers: ['Deep Purple', 'The Moody Blues', 'Jethro Tull', 'The Shadows'],
      corrAnsIndex: 2,
    },
  ],
};

export default questions;
